-Hey, here's your tip from Table 7.
-Oh, thanks.
(Penny:)-Mm-hm.
-Testing. Check. Check two.
(Bernadette:)Oh, now what?
(Penny:)-You want me to throw him out?
-No, that's okay.
(Penny:)Are you sure? He's small.
Bet I could get a nice tight spiral
on him.
I wanna dedicate this number
to a great gal who I've done wrong.
[SINGING]
Bernadette
(Howard:)I am so sorry
For trying to propose to you
(Penny:)Bernadette
(Howard:)You found it creepy
But that's just the kind of thing I do
Ahhh
(Howard:)I know now it was too soon
To talk of love
(Howard:)It was just a crazy idea
That came to me in my tub
(Howard:)But, Bernadette
Give me one more chance
(Howard:)Sweet Bernadette
(Howard:)I'll get the hang of this thing
They call romance
(Howard:)Sweet Bernadette
(Howard:)I dream to once again
Kiss your lips
(Howard:)Sweet Bernadette
(Howard:)Sincerely yours, Howard Wolowitz
(Penny:)Bernadette
(Penny:)Oh, I am so sorry.
(Bernadette:)Are you kidding?
(Bernadette:)That's the most romantic thing
anyone's ever done for me.
(Penny:)Bernadette
(Howard(still singing):)Thank you, Cheesecake Factory.
[CROWD CHEERS]